ADDY OSMANI: So build processes are important.
建设很重要。
Important because when you want to be fast,
重要，因为如果您想提高速度
you have to sort of give up the things that
您会放弃让自己慢下来的事情。
MATT GAUNT: T-shirt.
T恤衫。
It's a T-shirt slogan.
这是T恤徽标。
MATT GAUNT: Love it.
我喜欢
He says wearing a Yeoman T-shirt.
他说它穿着Yeoman T恤。
ADDY OSMANI: Product placement.
产品广告。
MATT GAUNT: [LAUGHS] But you're completely right.
但是你是绝对正确的。
Things like minifying your CSS and your JavaScript,
减少CSS和JavaScript
optimizing images.
和改进的图像
Like, all of that stuff is really laborious
他们都是令人生畏的事情
if you have to do it manually.
如果必须手动执行。
So getting it in your build process
因此，将它们插入到您的构建过程中
makes total sense, because just whenever you
很合逻辑，因为当
do a build of your site, it's just done, taken care of.
我建立了您的网站，它已经完成。
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah.
是的
This sort of fits into my three tiers of optimization tooling.
这与我的三个级别的优化工具是一致的。
I should make a pamphlet.
我应该写一本小册子。
MATT GAUNT: I feel like an advert
我觉得有一个广告
That's what it feels like right now.
那就是我现在的感觉。
ADDY OSMANI: It's life advice.
这是一生的建议。
See the difference?
你看到区别了吗？
OK.
知道了
So there's sort of a baseline of tools
有一个基准工具
that everybody should be doing these days.
这几天每个人都应该做。
Hashtag I hate.
我讨厌漫游数据费用。
I don't want anyone shipping 1,000 images down the line.
我不要任何人寄给我一千张照片。
So the baseline is you should be at least minifying
所以关键是你至少应该缩小
your styles and your JavaScript, optimizing your images,
模式，JavaScript和图像增强
using compression on the server side,
并使用服务器端压缩
using async scripts, leverage caching, [? weed ?] redirects.
并使用异步脚本并利用缓存优势，避免重定向。
That's the baseline.
这是基线。
Then we've got stuff that you and I have been exploring
然后我们有了我们正在探索的东西
a lot lately, which is sort of get fast and stay fast,
最近为了达到速度并保持
tools like things that'll help you in-line your critical path
它们是可以帮助您嵌入CSS关键路径的工具
CSS so that you can improve first render.
因此，您可以改进第一个演示文稿。
Things that will help you remove unused CSS.
可以帮助您删除未使用的CSS的东西。
MATT GAUNT: Like, a ton of those things-- what
这些东西很多-
I'm finding myself doing is I'm using the build process,
我正在做的是我正在使用构建过程
like building out custom, little things where basically, I
我制作定制的小东西
can still control what the critical path is,
使我能够控制什么是关键路径
and the build process is just helping me manage it.
只有施工过程才能帮助我进行管理。
Like, I know there are build process steps
我知道施工过程中有步骤
where it's like they'll do everything for you.
你为你做的一切。
And it's like magic.
就像魔术。
And that scares me, because I don't
吓到我了，因为我没有感觉
feel like I understand it enough to know whether those tools are
我足够了解它是否可以使用这些工具
doing the right thing or not.
做正确的事。
So I'm still in, like, the learning phase.
我还在学习。
But I'm using the build process just to make it easier
但是我使用构建过程只是为了使我更容易探索。
So there's Web Starter Kit.
有一个Web Starter Kit。
There's also Polymer Starter Kit, which
还有一个聚合物入门套件
is very similar to Web Starter Kit
它与Web Starter Kit非常相似
except it's got extra plugins specific to Polymer,
除了它们包含其他聚合物成分
like Vulcanize and things like that.
像硫化之类的东西。
But then Yeoman is basically like you can just go in
但是使用Yeoman，您只能登录
and it'll ask you what generator you want to use
系统将询问您要使用哪个发电机
is what they call, where you can then just
哪里可以
generate any style of project.
生成任何类型的项目。
So if you wanted to use something
如果你想使用一些东西
like Angular, or React, or whatever new hotness
像Angular或React或其他流行的东西，
is out there, chances are there's
它可能在那里
a generator that will give you a build process already
生成器实际上会为您提供构建
for those things.
对于那些东西。
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah.
是的，完全正确。
And like, one thing I find-- so we've
我发现的是-
got all of the baseline performance optimization
性能改善的所有基础
is pretty much covered by Web Starter Kit.
Web入门工具包涵盖。
One thing I find a lot of agencies doing
我发现很多代理商正在做的事情
is that they'll use Yeoman to scaffold out their projects.
是使用Yeoman为他们的项目创建支架。
And they'll go into Web Starter Kit, and they'll take a look
然后看一下Web Starter Kit
and say, OK, well, we're interested in the image
他们说：“嗯，我们对零件很感兴趣。”
optimization parts or the script minification parts.
与图像增强或文本缩小有关。
We're just going to steal, like, 70% of this file and just,
我们将挪用该文件的约70％
like, drop it into our project.
并将其放入我们的项目中。
And that's perfectly fine.
这是完全可以接受的。
Pick and choose what makes sense to you.
选择有意义的内容。
MATT GAUNT: So the way that I started doing this now--
所以我开始-
and I know you kind of don't agree with this approach.
我知道您不同意这种方法。
But I--
-但是我--我要走了。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah, you should.
是的，你应该。
So I have one Gulp file that, basically, you can do
我有一个Gulp文件，可让您执行
a thing like require-directory.
就像require-directory一样。
And then any JavaScript file within that directory,
然后该目录中的所有JavaScript文件
it will basically take the Gulp tasks
将承担Gulp任务
from those each individual files.
从每个单独的文件中。
And then you can basically use them
然后可以使用
as you would just one, big, long Gulp file.
好像只是一个很长的Gulp文件。
And the reason I'm doing that is you
真正的原因是
can split it out into styles, and scripts, and images.
它可以分为图案，文本和图像。
Like, each section will deal with its own thing.
每个部分将处理自己的部分。
And then I can copy those files into a new project,
然后我可以将这些文件复制到新项目中
delete any old ones that I don't want,
并删除我不需要的任何旧文件
and just change the directories.
并更改目录。
And it's like a really nice way of getting reuse out
这是重用的好方法
of my Gulp files, because before, when I had big ones,
我的Gulp文件是因为以前，当文件很大时
everything would just become messy.
一切都一团糟。
It'd be hard to maintain or understand where problems were.
很难维护或了解问题所在。
Whereas when I've got them in multiple files,
而当您将它们作为多个文件获得时，
everything just sort of becomes much easier
一切变得轻松多了
to manage, and maintain, and share.
在管理，维护和参与方面。
ADDY OSMANI: You've been demoted from colleague
您已被降级
to desk occupant.
到办公室常驻。
MATT GAUNT: Harsh.
太残忍了
ADDY OSMANI: This approach is actually pretty legit.
这种方法实际上是很合逻辑的。
If you're finding that you've got a really, really long Gulp
如果您发现Gulp文件过长，
file, splitting them out totally makes sense.
它的划分是很合逻辑的。
The reason we haven't done it in some of our boilerplate
我们在某些典型项目中没有这样做
projects is that for beginners, you
因为我们不想
don't want them to have to, like,
新生被迫
think about one other thing.
想一些额外的东西。
And it also gets a little bit trickier to debug if you've got
如果存在的话，更正错误也更加困难
multiple tasks and different files
多个任务和不同文件
that depend on each other.
互相依赖。
It's not a whole lot more, but it's just another thing
不多，但有些额外的东西
you've got to think about.
你会想到他的。
MATT GAUNT: Yeah.
是的
This is where I always get to a weird point of, like, best
在这里我到达一个奇怪的地方：
practice versus ease of use.
最佳实践与易用性。
ADDY OSMANI: Yeah.
是的
MATT GAUNT: And I always tend to go for best practice,
我总是倾向于选择最佳实践
because like, if you ever look at any of the native platforms,
因为如果您查看任何原始系统，
they always just say, this is the right way of doing
人们常说：这是正确的做法
something for this platform, or this ID, or library,
该平台，该ID或该库的内容
or whatever.
还是什么
There's no middle ground where you could do something,
没有让您做某事的妥协
because it's easier.
因为它更容易。
ADDY OSMANI: No, that's--
不，那-
MATT GAUNT: I'm not saying you're wrong, but--
我并不是说您错了，而是-
ADDY OSMANI: It's totally fair.
这很公平。
MATT GAUNT: I remember when we were-- like a little while ago,
我记得我们那时-不久前
you gave me a rundown of one of your presentations.
您给了我一份要约的摘要。
One of the bits was on build processes.
一部分是关于建筑的。
And you were like, everyone should just use Grunt.
您是说每个人都应该使用Grunt。
Actually, Gulp is coming out.
实际上，Gulp将被释放。
It's the new kid on the block.
这是现场最新消息。
It's kind of cool.
太棒了
Everyone should just use Gulp.
每个人都应该使用Gulp。
Actually, there's this new thing that's
其实有东西
kind of coming out called Broccoli
现代出版物《西兰花》。
that's also a build process.
建设也是一个过程。
Then again, [? MPM ?] scripts is also coming, so maybe use that.
另一方面，NPM文本也正在发布，因此请使用它
ADDY OSMANI: Yup.
是的
MATT GAUNT: And in my head, I realized-- this was at the time
我意识到-在那个时期
where I just learned Grunt and I was switching over to Gulp,
您刚刚学到了Grunt，而您将切换到Gulp
because it seemed like that was getting used a lot.
因为它似乎被广泛使用。
And I realized that, basically, all of the web tooling
我意识到所有系统工具都是网络
ecosystem is basically a "Game of Thrones," where the minute
基本上就像《权力的游戏》，
I fall in love with one, it's going to die and be replaced.
一旦她爱上了一个人，他就死了并且被替换了。
So there's a bit of me that feels like I should just
所以我的一部分感到我不应该
never get attached to any of my tools, because sooner or later,
附加到我的任何工具，因为迟早
by getting attached, I'm almost dooming it.
我的担心已成必然。